<?xml version='1.0' encoding="UTF-8"?>
<div>
  <table border='1px' align='center'>
    <tr>
      <td/>Fast Pizza
      <td/>10 min.
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td/>Pizza from Scratch
      <td/>15 min.
    </tr>
    <tr>
      <td/>Popular Toppings
      <td/>25 min.
    </tr>
  </table>
  <div  id='firstBlock'>
    <p>
      <h4>Fast Pizza</h4>
    </p>
    <p>
      <h2>1</h2>Preheat the oven to 400°F (204°C). 
      The oven should be piping hot before you start cooking the pizza.
    </p>
    <p>
      <h2>2</h2>Prepare the crust. Remove the unbaked crust from the packaging. Place it on a round or rectangular baking sheet, 
      depending on what you have on hand. Use a pastry brush to spread a thin coating of olive oil over the top of the crust.
    </p>
    <p>
      <h2>3</h2>Spread pizza sauce on the crust. How much pizza sauce you add is purely a matter of personal preference. 
      If you love a lot of sauce, go ahead and slather it on. If you prefer your pizza on the dry side, spoon a little in the middle and spread it around in a thin layer.
      <ul>
        <li>
          If you want to make a white pizza, add a little extra olive oil and skip the pizza sauce.
        </li>
        <li>
          You can make a quick pizza sauce using tomato paste, a can of diced tomatoes, and some spices. 
          Simmer the paste and tomatoes (without draining them first) together over low heat. Add salt, oregano and pepper to taste. Continue simmering until the sauce cooks down to the consistency of pizza sauce.
        </li>
      </ul>
    </p>
    <p>
      <h2>4</h2>Add toppings. Layer your favorite toppings over the sauce. Add as many or as few toppings as you want. 
      Put the heavier toppings, like onions, chicken or sausage, on the bottom layer, and add lighter toppings, like spinach leaves or peppers, on the top layer. Continue until your pizza is loaded with the amount of toppings you like
    </p>
    <p>
      <h2>5</h2>Add the cheese. Sprinkle mozzarella cheese over the toppings. Layer it on thick if you 
      like it that way, or add a thin layer if you're going for a lighter pizza.
    </p>
    <p>
      <h2>6</h2>Cook the pizza. Place the pizza in the oven for about 20 minutes, or until the crust is 
      golden brown and the cheese is melted. Remove it from the oven and allow it to cool for a few minutes before slicing.
    </p>
  </div>
</div>